Voices collide, the storm and the flame Laughter and chaos, it's part of the game
Secrets unravel, the stage is alive In Psyche's arena, the strange will survive
Who's afraid?
Let it break from shadows to starlight
The truth will be shown
The psyche awakens
You're never alone
Expect the unexpected
Strange and unusual
Step inside the flow
The circus of shadows
It's Psyche's show
Terrible trolls in the dark
Take their stand
But angels are dancing
Cheers to the friends, the story gets stranger, it never ends
Awaken
Psychies show
I've heard this show, maybe I can change my color.
Let's bring my, like, hey, what's up, guys?
Hello.
Hi, Nancy, Jamie's Cowboys.
Reality Nancy.
Hey, hello.
Reside.
Yeah, gotta look proud, gatherer.
How are we guys doing?
I'm tired of, oh, look it, I got the kick people already here.
It's really good.
Let me look in the comment and let you talk.
I'm actually, let's have a little hiding place.
Let's see if there's anything.
Said, they said, what'd they say?
I need my glasses.
It's it soon
That's all menace. Hey guys, what's up guys? Okay, so
See
No, I I know I have like
Show with law the biggest trolls, you know what I like you guys
Hey, babe, I'm really came up say hi
I mean, it depends on my mood, I mean, in bad moods, right?
I mean, it's like, at least like everybody knows
gets the trolling kind of stuff.
Like, it's like no one really gets that offended
because it's like, people know what they're getting into
at least, and so it's like, and then maybe people learn
how to deal with trolls, like if you can like deal
with my show, I'll like deal with any show.
You can go party to any show and like be able to like.
If you watch enough of my show you'll know what I'm talking about you can go go by the way to see my
my community page and
Chris summary is on there and
I mean, it's like from like four months ago
I wish you for and it's just so funny you have to watch it's
But she's like she's like you are bad person. Let's see. Yeah, it's like what?
She's like
Yeah, you're not as nice as everyone, and then she's like, I'm a mind reader.
Yeah, it really is.
But I have to admit, oh look, this is what my TikTok is like.
See, it's like, and you're like, you can have like all this kind of...
Well, you can, I can do that now here too, but I say I do really fast readings.
I just do readings on there.
So, if you want a free reading, go to TikTok.
If you want a page reading, I'll do the page readings here because...
I think that's a better play, but also pull a card is what I ask for you know, the general
reads too, but it is like it is a lot of energy I expend even for you know short reads, but
really like stupid, oh yeah he's 16 years old, he likes to think like, hey man, there's
And Alex is such a jerk because I was like I'm picking up Rudy's like oh my god the cat hates
He's trying to get away. The cat is not trying to get away. Love
Okay, now it's good now you can go back. I'm
Then I would cats are like that, right? No, he's right here, so
Hello, you look camera shy you're on straight one on your channel or what?
Oh, this channel
No, well, I don't know
Last night
It's like you know, there's things that just like energy attacks and like
things like that and so
It's like there's always something there if you like are looking for it, right?
And so it's like if you don't pay attention to it, then it's like
Yeah, by the way, I just smoked pot. I just smoked the
poppies. Oh
My god
Like a mess over and I was like, yeah, no the bag is like the alcohol
Yeah, I think I stick when I haven't had like pretty good meat like a good I had like some really crappy wings that I
But this is expensive well not too expensive 25 for like a gram, and I got two of those
And look up all
Let's see
It's got heart come on
Brand new guy. Oh, yeah, I was gonna say I remember was it I get so high I got distracted. That's why I don't
Let's see oh
Yeah, I should go to my own chef my chef's the only safe one I can go to actually
Well, it's not even that safe
Okay, you know in my even baseball
Like people go on time out and then they like, you know, sometimes I call them back out of the dugout. I
Don't know how this all works. Just stop by say hi. Hi, sweetheart. Amanda. I think people like to clean to my show
Oh my gosh, and they stands with rugs, etc. Yeah, oh my gosh
I used to have that being the camera and so
Hi, let's see, hello, something will happen eventually, so let's see, I have like a lot
of, I actually, I don't know if you've heard like the older songs, like the older songs
I think, like, you know, I need to cut back on my subscriptions and stuff like that and all these things, you know.
But, we all could just make sure you don't get double-filled.
Credit card companies are usually pretty good about doing that.
Let's see. Okay, I'll play some, I'll play like an old song.
Let me see, oh my god, hello, let me see.
Javid?
Okay.
Oh, this one, I once wrote a song about the rules of the show.
I don't know if that's how it was.
Hmm, and community, yeah, I bring.
But I do have uh, oh, yeah, here's the rules
No hate speech don't test that line don't care if it's soft day to hard our time you say it you gone
Don't play confuse this ain't that show we don't make those moves. No slander
Yeah, I said what I said you toss more fake dirt than a reddit thread
WWE got nothing on this chat false accusations man cut that crap
You better
Oh, no, it's it repeated. Oh shit. I know
Do you remember by the way?
Oh yeah, I still remember by myself.
Okay.
I also, just nobody's coming up with me.
It's like, I'm fun to talk to.
I'm like, hi, because I'll just probably let you talk
because it's a lot.
But, I can just, all I can do is play songs.
These are all my music though.
Let's see.
Well.
What else do you have?
I think that's a good one, that was a really good one, let's see, well let's see, the other
You've probably seen it, you've probably seen it.
I mean, it's like the way they come out is like,
I just think kind of let it do its thing
because this is really like fast,
expensive, very smart program that does that.
I mean, it's like, if you see how amazing,
it's like such amazing looking.
But you know it doesn't make sense some of the time because they'll just be like weird little shit like things in the video
I think that's like part of their like
charm, you know
But I really don't put it's like I put the lyrics
I don't put the lyrics in that but it's like it's already in a song form right and so then
It transcribes the lyrics
And, oh, here we go, so that's right.
It's my Ireland, let me see.
Do I know you?
I'm not gonna put you on until I see something.
I just see a blank, a ceiling.
There's another ceiling.
You know what I'm saying?
I see a shadow, a shadow.
Who are you?
Or the backstage who you are,
or in the chat who you are, I don't see.
Who is it?
Ah, a channel.
You see, see who this person backstage is.
You see.
Oh, it's so young.
Now they're sitting there.
Well, that's me.
Hold on.
There's a little backstage.
Oh my God.
Hello
Hey, how are you? Can you hear me?
Yeah, you oh
Sweet hello, it's Glenn. My name is Glenn from Dublin, Ireland. How's things? Oh?
Wow good. Hold on. How'd you find my show?
I've actually been subscribed to your show for a good few months now. I know this is a little bit jarring having them
Give me just one second
Staring at my ceiling is a little bit jarring. I do know that so let me try to see if I can do something about that
Yeah, so for the past couple of months, I've actually seen your show
There's not seem to be much I can do about that, but yes in any case I see the
debates and the twos and the froze
and all that good stuff that happens on the show.
I've never joined the chat or jumped in,
but I'm a little bit pissed off at the moment.
So I just thought, you know what?
Now's as good as time as any to just jump in and say hello.
Oh, cool.
You've never been on the show before?
Sorry say that again. Have you ever been on the show before like every year? No, not this one in particular my friend
And but I've been on other people's stream yard
So I'm a kind of like a little bit accustomed to stream yards
I've actually just tried the fucking change boy. Sorry excuse my language
Yeah, I don't want to ruin anybody's monetization board
Yeah, of course, yeah, yeah never yeah, yeah
Well, how's things anyway? How's the night going? Is everything all right?
Yeah
Nah, not too bad. Not too bad. I don't smoke myself, but I make up for it with drink, you know
Hmm. Oh, yeah. Well, I'm drinking too. I'm having a
strawberry pineapple
harder lemonade
Hey, not too bad. So what's the strength of that? Is that a daiquiri?
It's like 8% alcohol
And so it's just no not too bad
Yeah, yeah, so that's kind of like what we have over here is like a
Well, they call it over here for local or something like that. It's like a
caffeinated beverage with it with a bit of a bit of spice to it a bit of a kick to it
alcohol percentage wise
But it's nothing too crazy like you would have to have a generous amount of them to
Kind of get off your tits as it were, but um
Especially if you were seasoned a seasoned drinker like myself like one or two with us bad boys would be like a refreshment
I'd need about six or seven before I start feeling a little bit liquored up
You get me. Yeah. Yeah, I guess you like yeah
I know what to do with your channels all about and I've seen that I've seen like
You can have like six, eight people on your panel at times, it gets a bit crazy.
So I guess for you now, it's like, you're pretty early, like not in the, what, in the afternoon?
I think towards the evening.
I stream like all day like you know early or not all day, but I stream a little bit less than I used to
I used to stream all day every day for like
And like you get really drunk, but I've been like, you know a little bit less but
What do you know are you are you like are you like afternoon towards the evening now like so like 4 p.m. Or something like that
Yeah, this all through the day like
Yeah, I tend to I tend to agree with that a little bit like I try to look at the clock as
Like the least amount of times that I can because it just like
Depresses me to be fair
But like at the moment if I look at the clock here in Dublin, Ireland, it's real depressing
Well, it'd be worse if it was like a Sunday night going into a Monday morning where the kids at school or wherever
But at the moment, it's Friday night going into a Saturday morning and it's 6 34 a.m
So that gives us 25 minutes to 7am but listen the best thing is I ain't got shit to do tomorrow
so I can wake up at whatever time I want you know so that's okay for me like this weekend it's
gonna be okay
If that was if this was Sunday night, it would be catastrophic
But I would never we were okay. I love those headphones point away every time I see them
I'm like, I've never seen those before like I never seen any streamer have them before these LED lights on those headphones
Are they very rig real good headphones? They look they look good
Yeah, well, and I think you know, it's kind of like, you know, there's those really expensive headphones like out there
Of course like $300 is like you know people were paying for like some but yeah, I couldn't just
Yeah, they're very good quality like I mean I've had this for like months as long, you know, the microphone is fine
It's just like I'm kind of like slow sometimes
But I do are you readings? I don't know if you want me to pull up your cards for you
I'm like well, I'll tell you what I've actually never had a reading done before and
When I see you do them I'm like Jesus
It's you know the way you get some people who are inquisitive
And then you get some people who are like really curious and then you get some people who did they don't that
They'll just go through their whole lives without ever wondering why I'm one of those people so
So, yeah, I'll actually, well, if I could, yeah, okay, let's, let's do it then, if that's okay.
Okay, I'm gonna shut the cards. You can like, I'm curious. I'll say that much. It's not,
you know, when the curiosity never reaches a certain point where you go and you seek that,
like, I like your channel because of the debates and stuff like that. But as I'm here,
while I'm here, let's do it. Let's do it. That'd be nice.
Okay, I'll put you a few cards, like just like maybe three and then maybe like...
Thank you my friend, I appreciate it.
It's Glenn from Dublin by the way, people.
I think everybody loves Dublin Ireland.
Yeah, everybody loves the Irish.
Yeah, I wish Joe was here right now. Joe's usually here. Oh, is he part Irish? Yeah
Yeah, well, he's uh, you know, he has red hair
It must make
He's gonna be some kind of Irish
Okay, he's probably yeah shipping up the Boston whoa
That's not even an Irish band song, by the way, that's just like there's a there's a there's a movie called the Boondock Saints or something
and there's like an Irish tinge in it, like regarding the history and the story of it, but the Dropkick Morpheus made it made the musicals, yeah, they ain't Irish, but I'd love to claim them, I love the Dropkick Morpheus, I'd love to claim them, I've been to see them live in Dublin, they were great
of the
We have the two of swords, and so this isn't like a past position. There's two of swords
There's a blind spot. There's also a cross at a crossroads to and like also it may involve cutting something out
trying to cut something out
but
You know, it's about not seeing the whole picture at the time because then we have
We have the five of swords and this is like some kind of like really bad heartbreak or like actually like
Like a lot of like fighting but there's like a bit of that's actually crazy
That is crazy because I've got a very small family and I don't know anybody really in my dad's side, but in my mom's side
I did my mom's my mom's siblings
She has five sisters and six brothers and one of one of her sisters actually lives in a place called swords like SWO or DS in Dublin and
and
something real crazy happened in the past three years where the husband which is like
The husband actually is in prison at the moment because of like fighting that was happening and it's kind of big news in Dublin
Like it's like that kina and hutch kind of thing that was going on my family kind of it closely related to that and
one of my uncles is
Is in prison for something that was related to that and he's from swords. Yeah, that's that's absolutely mental
What the hell?
Already first card you're killing me
And the and this but the five of sorts is also like kind of like, you know
You know, she has like I was like it takes one's head off. Maybe like early on someone like
No, no, um, well Jesus see then you know when you have to kind of pause for a second and see now
Nothing to do with like taking anybody's head off for
Like I wouldn't take
What happened in the Regency Hotel in in in Ireland and in Dublin, New Orleans and it was nothing to do with like
Okay, so the rich so how I could relate that if I had to like reach into it
what they try to do and
This faction of the gang
Try to take off the head like you say that people say like the head of the snake off of off of like the
The what what do we what do they call it like the gang organization they go for the head and
Like they go for like the top the top person. That actually was what happened on the day. They tried to go for that. Yeah
That's actually quite a nut. I thought if anybody ever did this to me one day
I have to say I'm skeptical. I said this is not gonna work on me, but I'm sitting here right now
You pulled out the swords and you talk. Yeah, that's absolutely crazy
I have not stayed in my family were deeply involved in it to the extent that my family were involved in it
My uncle is a taxi driver, and he was like a getaway person. It's not a shit. It's not something. I'm proud of
Obviously, but that is an actual fact and I'm gonna I'm gonna relate to what you say what you pull the cards out
I'm gonna say it
With it and because I also like I just like glance at the bottom of the deck and this was there and it's like
You know, it's like a woman walking away. It's supposed to be maybe this
Justice or something like that, but I was trying to find my glasses. What is that one again?
This is why I saw the justice card at the bottom of the deck just when I you know
I said I'm sick the other cars will come up during the reading
I just thought it was interesting because it's like this one has like okay
This one is like the first she's like walking away or she'll get away with it or something like that and okay
We'll see. Yeah. Well, well, well, well then maybe maybe that's what it is because like I said my
Jesus, we don't let anybody know who I am my my
My uncle's role in the whole thing was he was actually a taxi driver in Dublin city center
And he knew the people who were going to do the thing
And then he decided like that he was gonna be part of the getaway crew
Like so he decided he was gonna walk get away with it like like you have a small
implication but then get away with the
and with the thing which is a terrible thing by the way people
i hope i'm not speaking about this in a blasé way i'm just trying to be honest
uh to to what these cards mean to me
and this person in my my personal life i don't speak to
at all haven't done since i was like well for 25 years
and it means it doesn't represent me in my life
And then there's like there's this we have the two of wands and it says are you prepared for your journey?
And so, and we have like, I don't know if you can see it.
Is it kind of like a vampire guy?
Is it like power, is it like new, is it like power?
It's like, I was also like, you know,
two of wands could be about coming together
with another person with like the same passion
and like, you know, having the manifest.
It's like something powerful.
And then we have this, we have this,
see this is the four of Pentacle,
and this is called the Collector.
And so, collecting something,
I think maybe you collect, like, I don't know what it means
when you see it, or if you're a collector of something.
This is, as the four pentacles, yeah, it's just, it could be memories, or it could be
like something specific.
So pentacles, what would you attribute to that word, pentacles, I'm trying to think
about that myself now.
The pentacle is like, you know, it's a circle with the pentagram inside of it.
It represents money, it represents the material world, like the earth, you know, the pinnacles
are the suit of the earth, right?
And so...
Well, what I would say about me, what's unique and outstanding about me, me myself, I met
my partner like nearly 15 years ago now and she was actually deaf and she's from a family
two of my three kids are actually deaf and nobody else in my actual like bloodline are actually
deaf so we kind of merged together and to this day we we we we forged the union didn't we that's
what we did and and we we've powered forward with the with the kids and so and so I don't know
Definitely like there's a joint venture there with myself and my partner and that's always a consideration
You know the difficulties in the this and the disabilities and stuff like that. So maybe there's a connection with that
I also see like, you know
A collector of like, I don't know maybe of ex-girlfriends or something like that. I think I'm just getting an idea of that
like I don't think a lot of exes ex-girlfriends or
Well, yeah, I guess
I guess beyond the 15 years there was there was a couple. Yeah, there was a there was a few and there was a couple that I'm still
I guess hung up on but I obviously try not to dwell on it too much these days
But yeah, there was period in my life there where they were the one. Yeah, you know, I'm talking about they were the one
But then they weren't and then there's always the hang-up period
period of 15 years later and
It doesn't mean to say that I don't still have these like cold sweats where I wake up in the middle of the night and go
What if?
you know but yeah so that's definitely a thing yeah 100% yeah and then we have like uh we then
we have uh the uh page of swords and it's an interesting card like it's like another like
I just get so much energy of late
Oh, like well, I think we're pages swords is like the spy card, you know, usually like somebody's watching you
And I think okay in a reversal as they can be like sometimes I think if it's this reverse
I'd be like it would just make it worse
So it's like it's in the upright and so it's like it could be just say someone's looking at you into your progress about something
Okay, also, maybe like I love a woman a woman may be a control of your fate or something like that
Yeah, maybe maybe that's my mom and maybe that's my mom
Her name is Diane actually and well I'm going to be 40 in December, I lost her when I was 12
I'm the oldest of three siblings, yeah three siblings had a double take there for a second
I'm the oldest of three siblings and she always did say to me like you know like
Even it like she wrote a letter and saying like you are the oldest one
So make sure like everyone stays together stays united
And so I've always felt that pressure and it's not that I've ever said it to my siblings
It's just it's something that I I felt without saying it and so I always feel
That that kind of like somebody's watching over me like telling me like
Just try and do as best you can because you're the leading shining light. You're the example
That's so to me if I was to relate that that's what I would say because I always do feel that pressure
Even though I was 12 years old when I received that letter and I'm like what 28 28 years on now and
That always stuck with me that the suit that she's watching and I have to hold a certain standard because if I'm going to
To be okay in my life and I set the bar that high then if they fell short of it or whatever
They wouldn't be too far off and they wouldn't do too badly, you know
Yeah, I'm probably gibberish. I'm tough. I'm probably talking a lot of gibberish, but I'm definitely talking truthfully and
I'm trying to relate it as best as I can to what you're telling me
Because yeah, well, you have one final card and it's like, you know
One of the better one of the better cards to get as opposed like as a conclusion of the reading which is the 10 of cups
Okay, you know, this is a picture of the family, you know, it's like a black and white family. Yes. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah
This is like, but it's like it's like the 10 of Cubs is like the ultimate happiness card
It works they ultimately you'll be happy ultimately
It was like they'll be a happy family and it will be like a good environment and yeah
Yeah, and and it's just seems like it's just a positive sign in a really that you're exactly it's actually quite interesting you say that
say that and show that to me right now because this is basically a by chance and coincidental my
my kids actually went with their auntie and their whole husband camping since Wednesday till Friday
right and then they went back home today to
My my partner's mother's house is which is in Bray County, Wicklow, Ireland
Which is like 30 kilometers away from where I live
But anyway myself and my partner who have been with for 15 years have been here alone in the house for the past
Since Wednesday, and we've just felt a
complete sense of a very like avoid a whole missing in the house
And we've like we're enjoying our company just us together like it was in the beginning. Yeah
but we've felt the chasm that that's been left since the kids weren't here and that's all she
kept saying to me she was like it's crazy when the hair like it's madness and i love the break
away like when they're not here like it's nice to have a kind of a little break away from what she
said the the absence of them not being here is horrible so and it made me think i was like you
it just made me feel more appreciative of them. You know when someone's living with you like 24-7
you can kind of lose the sense of gratitude or whatever it is, but when they're away from you
like for a couple of days, I guess like when you lose somebody in your family that's real close to
it, you do get that sense of wholesomeness, that sense of home, and home is not just the four walls
Home that you live in. Yeah. So to me, that's what that means. Um, I
Didn't really know how much I missed the people that I lived with all the time until I didn't live with them anymore for a few days
And today yeah, that was an eye opener for me today. That happened today
Family man, eh
Yeah, family and like but it's all yeah happy family. It's like, you know, usually just say a lot of people buy a pool like celebrate
Yeah, so that's what as soon as they came home, you know the first thing I talked about when they came home
Was like I can't wait till we get you know decorations up for Halloween and stuff like that
You wouldn't believe how crazy is over here Brown Thomas in Dublin City Center
have started putting the christmas trees up and on now so they're already getting the christmas
trees going it's crazy over here man the christmas trees going really good good god it's not even
the end of summer like really well i guess we're coming into autumn right now but what i want to
say is thank you so much for that reading i was pessimistic to say the least but every single
thing you've just said there from the beginning with the card that said swords which is
That's just blown my mind like, yes, thank you so much for doing that and taking the
time to do that from me.
I really do appreciate it.
Oh, yeah, it's a great meeting you're hopefully you'll come up again and like...
You know, I love the new people, you know, you're the person of the panel, like sometimes we've had just like not many new people in the panel lately, so it's nice to meet a new person, a nice, interesting guy, like, and I'm very nice, because the decision is nice, you like, you didn't troll at all, it hurt like, you know, just...
No, not at all. And by the way, I'd like to recommend people, you know, along the way.
Over over time to you know cuz cuz I know I meet a lot of people in my life
My life who are very spiritual minded and something like this would mean a lot to them
Like I didn't even realize that that was something that I'd I'd I was I was like nah come on man
How how am I gonna be able to relate to this?
But it's like when you stress when you start speaking to someone and then all of a sudden
It's just that's like making sense. That's that's remarkable to me. So
I've got a lot of spiritual minded people in my life, and I'll definitely
send them your way, and I'm gonna keep obviously tuned into your channel.
I do, I do love your channel. I've been following it for the past,
I'd say about 8 to 10 months. So yeah, you keep doing your thing, mate,
and thank you so much for having me on tonight.
What do you follow?
What about you, man?
Have a great day, bless you. Thank you so much.
Thank you.
Peace.
Yeah, so I can play with some of these effects.
I can show you some art, actually, now that I have
like this stuff on the stream here.
I have all these really cool visual things.
So let's see what I have in my repertoire.
I don't want to add so much stuff here.
Let's see.
I think I can show you.
I want to show you.
I'm just going to show you, so I'm going to keep setting things.
Let's see here.
Oh my god, I'm a little bit too high to figure this out right now, but I'll just do it.
It's in the back Emma, there you will get back to where it's located, so it's okay to have it.
There was a mod in the land of tarot dreams
Wild in the ranch like a sword in the stream
Emma Leviathan, demon, queen, divine
Read the cards, stole my soul and crossed the line
I was a mod in the land of tarot dreams
Wield in the wrench like a sword in the stream
Emma Leviathan, demon queen divine
Read the cards, stole my soul and crossed the line
She was Satan's ex with that fiery stare
Stuck in hell
He's in his Speedos stars and stripes parade fish tacos on the table another wild charade
He's hitting on the straight men come on lose that shirt meanwhile beat us on the hotline yelling till
Persian functions petty poetic justice data came through with a tray and a smirk talking about biscuits like she did the work
But baby those scones are drier than Tehran. Where's the honey sauce girl? It's gone
You say you're the queen of the big off crew, but your butter slipped out like it's dodging you
I've got saffron cardamom rosewater drizzle you brought confusion and a half-baked fizzle
Low smooth mystical from the shadows of the sub conscious to the chaos of the cosmic scrolls
This is psyche awakens crown whoosh
sparkly chimes
Thundercrack
Yeah, yeah
Yeah, yeah, yeah, welcome to the madness buckle in tight tarry on death third eye and fly
Trolls be dropping spirits in the chat and the vibes ain't stopping the noise on guard tricks bring in love
Lola Rudy marbles fan from above
I've been missing in my sleep
flame laughter and chaos it's part of the game secrets unravel the stage is
alive and psyches arena the strange will survive who's awake we're awake who's
afraid let it break from shadows to starlight the truth will be shown the
Strange and unusual, step inside the flow, the circus of shadows, it's Psyche's show.
Terrible trolls in the dark take their stand, but angels...
psyche's show
I'm sorry, I was just, I was just, hi, I'm just watching.
Right, you're Alison Underland?
I know, I'm gonna try to put the other,
like, I'll try other versions of like the lyrics
that I'm into the lyrics.
I think they sound good.
I'm gonna try other versions of music, too.
And maybe like someone, I might,
no, you definitely used my credits, so you're just
so obsessed.
Maybe you used some of the videos, too.
I don't know.
Oh, hey, Alan Orchard, sweetie.
Shut up to key cats
I don't know, like we don't, I don't know what to do. Yeah, yeah, I'm, uh, I don't know, I think, uh, I have to see what's going on. Shut up.
Yeah, I guess I'm gonna, I'm, I'm sorry to show up tonight, I'm not, I'm not too many people, so, you'd have a nice guest, and,
so there's some music, I don't know, I'm sorry, there's a room left.
I guess everyone's going to beat us, I'm sorry, I didn't mean to take away from the
beat us show.
Guys, just go beat us chat, I'll finish it real quick.
Like my heart. Oh, I love it on Amazon
Really cool
Oh my god, I've never seen anything like that
It holds you
Really be here
I want to go over there
Just maybe like you can make a picture too
What is that?
I've really been like, you know, take a chance
But I love gymnics, I don't know if you guys know gymnics, but I really want to go support
gymnics right now because, you know, she's going through a tough time, and, you know,
I see she gets bullied and stuff like that, maybe taking advantage of, or like, you know,
some people aren't that nice to gymnics, I really want to like, maybe like...
go, just say hi to Jimmick on Vita's panel, and I also like, I like to go to Vita's and
I said like, hey, I'm sorry right now, when she was gone, you know, I'm not like, it's
hard to take her audience, but it's like, just because like, Bronzeberg and Gautam's
are up there and I was, I didn't feel like talking to them, and I wanted some people
to come over here if they wanted to check me out, but it's, I mean, I say, I want, basically
I want people to check me out.
and, you know, definitely go to her.
So, too much drama over there, Taylor, you think?
Well, it just like hanging out in the chat, maybe,
and I see what's going on.
It's like, I think she's just having
a friendly conversation with Jimnick right now.
But I like Jimnick a lot.
Like, I had like a, I went on Jimnick's show,
she had the show, and she, okay, so I'll tell the story.
Like, I hope, let me see if I can ask her,
if I can like put up, I can't shoot.
I can actually put up a video now.
Let me see if I can, like, I'll ask her.
Oh, no.
I think, I think we'll just go over there.
I don't know. I'll go over there.
Yeah, go over there and be this channel if you can, okay?
I'll be back here, too, but check me out there.
I'm going to be on her panel.